Hello everyone Whatsapp how are you
wish good Jakas Bindass amazing and the
admission of MM University has started so if
you are a student of Bihar or
any other student then
before taking admission it is
important for us to know how many lakhs the placement has been done in the college
so brother I am hearing that it is also
70 lakhs and even 80 lakhs so what
is the reality, is there any
placement after studying from MM University or not, it is going to be
clear to you in today's video,
along with this I will tell you that the
scam that is happening in admission which I had
brought in the previous video about how the counselor
scams, if you want to get
admission in an authentic way by avoiding all those things,
you want to get admission with a trustworthy person so that
if you get admission then
your seat is confirmed and
if you need
someone to accompany you in your journey to the hostel, that is from home to the hostel, then
you
can take admission through any student or  It
could be your brother or sister or
anyone could be your friend, RC
neighbor, any friend should be there,
do not get admission through a counselor, I am just
saying this much, if you do not have any friend then you
can call me on the number given on the screen or then
in the description box below, brother,
we are going to talk about the placement of MM University,
what is its scene, how much has the highest package of MM
University placement gone, right now as
I have seen the board, 42 LPA means 442
lakhs brother, his package went to the company
etc. so I will share it with you guys,
I share it on Instagram2,
whatever company is there here and
MMDU Mullana
updates its own pay and everything happens and
if you guys also want that whatever
placements happen, bring videos of them in series by series,
I will ask about the journey of any child who gets placed so
far, then brother you can comment in the comment box below,
if you get 10 to 15 comments saying
yes brother, you should make a series of placements  How did you feel about someone,
take his interview, what
is the system like, what did he face in his life,
after all, what is asked in placement,
what should we do related to the course, if
you guys want to know all those things then you
can comment in the comment box below
and you can do it here related to admission, so
if you guys want placement then
in today's video I have come to say only this that
if you guys want placement series
videos then you
can comment and as for the rest of the placement, the
college gives very good placements overall,
if we talk about B.Tech CS Chem placement then it has gone up to
42 lakhs, if we talk about normal BBA
placement, if we
talk about average placement then 3 lakhs is
going to be the minimum right now and if we
talk about average within average also, average within average
means that if you assume that it is a little more than the minimum
and a little less than the highest then
their placement is of 6-7 lakhs,
my own placement has come,
my BBA roommate is also my friend and they are
also BBA BCM, so  The
placements that are coming from them, so far whatever
placements I have seen,
I have seen placements ranging from 2 lakhs to 9 lakhs
which is the reality, if you ask then I will send you my
screenshot.